[BLANK_AUDIO]
Okay, just to say you're riding a car with your going along trip.
This is an unknown circumstance, you can fare your way to the car.
We'll get the ammo, the car.
In a way, the car will just stop the seat in front of you.
There's nothing to answer.
You'll do the first hand.
They'll do the first hand in your head.
They'll have an amount of the car.
Possibly the driver.
You can stop the car and go somewhere in prayer to be better.
You have to catch a certain appointment and you're late and nobody can stop.
You still travel the city to sell.
What about you standing with an unemployment woman?
And you're in your genome, you can close to a...
How can you come?
You can't get anywhere.
So a lot of players, the one watching, there's absolute in order, excuse for not to...
You can't think of anything. You cannot. There's absolutely no way. You can say, "I won't
do this or you won't do that."
You see. Even when you're sick, if you're part of the Legion, you can play with your ideas.
It's hard to do that, but when I'm with you, you can go up and go.
and it's really hard to trust that you can understand it up and stand it.
No, but it's doing it in your head.
It's just a drop of space.
-You have to go out to the door.
-Yes.
-You'll be right there.
So...
-I'm not.
-I'm in the night.
So, I sit right there on Tuesday,
working all after the one.
All four o'clock, I'm happy to stop.
-I'm in the night.
-And I'm moving too busy.
I think it's a great idea to just praise myself.
I don't have to worry about it already.
Thank you.
It's more an hour to learn about things you want.
If you better, if you don't make it, we'll do it.
We'll find the flag just to try it.
It's a good moment.
But if it's not possible, yes, it can pay up to this.
It's especially good.
If you're scrambling, you want to go on a bus, for example, on a plane.
Right.
We need to do it in a lot of the holidays.
You know, two, three lines of verse is very wide, you know, under abnormal circumstances.
And you are the one who can judge what you can or cannot do.
You cannot cheat yourself.
If you are in any way able to do the selection in the normal way, do it that way.
Otherwise you'll be cheating yourself.
You say, "Oh, I can't do it that way."
You're going to keep the children on the heart and get quiet.
(speaking in foreign language)
(indistinct chatter)
Thomas, sit next to that.
[ Laughter ]
[ Inaudible ]
You're the only one together way to make noise.
On the next sub-fighting, I don't know, that's not my section, but just want to point out that the Quran goes out of this way to guarantee the rights of the women.
A lot of people around the world can feel.
(crowd talking)
- That's what the book is going.
So I can bet it will come from here, Isaac.
(crowd cheering)
Come here, Isaac.
People around the world are confusing.
The traditions that our government and the Hispanic world
forgot the parameters.
It's a big role, but at this time,
our press is women.
But the opposite is exactly true.
As you see here, the alimony for widows
and divorcees is for Alec and John.
So who wants to take the next?
Three verses.
The two, do you want to go?
Those more you to die and leave widows behind,
send the praise to the last four four gildums,
the last ones, right for years.
The firetakes, they choose to stay in the husband's household.
It takes you to leave, then you enter the sin,
the letting them do whatever they use.
So long as they are meant to die to both of you.
That is all right, be wise.
For the D4C's equitable elimination of the providing,
this is an incumbent duty for the right-hand.
There are thousands of players,
there are places for you that you might understand.
This 240 tells us that the
The widow that was asked on the set, it was the widow's date in the husband's house,
She is entitled to one year support.
But if you can see this here, from the husband, you have to make sure that he is leaving enough support for the widow, for his widow or widows to ask what he is, support not to one year.
[ Inaudible ]
(indistinct)
>> [INAUDIBLE]
(indistinct chatter)
- The widow was supposed to get one floor from the state.
So we go.
It's supposed to get one floor from the state.
And what is the big kids to meet with the house?
If they get to the marriage, then they will leave the house
home means he wants to go back to our father's house
and wants to marry or something.
It's a struggle for anyone, it's like a struggle for anyone, it's a struggle for a call.
But is that part of the chair be safe?
No, it's a, it could be a mess, it could be a service.
The idea is not, is that when a man marries a woman, she's not the same anymore.
And she may become dependent on her at least partially.
So the idea is to burn tea hearts a year of history of support.
Because she loves for something else.
I'm going to say something on this street.
So this is my reputation because this is something that we actually need these cases in a country.
I'm just going to tell you what they do in our country.
This has nothing to do with inheritance of the widow.
In our country where families live together, you know,
it's not just a nuclear family.
In the household you have brother, sisters and so on.
She has a share of inheritance.
That is something else.
You may interpret this as follows.
Somebody takes over the household.
Maybe it's a son or a brother of the deceased.
That widow, if she remained in the household, must be guaranteed to court for at least one year.
unless she decides to go back to her father or to her brother or she has enough means of her own and she wants to
independence and she gets her children with her.
Let's take my case.
Let's say I die and the one who takes over the more
or less the responsibility of the household
where they all live together.
He, normally he's a brother or an oldest son,
he must take care of my guarantee, my widow,
for at least one year.
And I think that is very close to this.
Over and above the inheritance.
But if she doesn't want to stay,
can get her in her hands and live.
And the head of the household is not
obliged now to feed her in another household,
because she has left the household.
She's standing here.
If you want me to feed you for one year, you stay.
But if you go, then you're on your own.
Maybe you want to do what you want.
Or maybe she has a prospective husband.
So give her a chance to go.
The Quran is designed to cover all circumstances.
The other consensus is that if the inheritance laws cover the one-year support for the wife,
then there's no need to worry about it.
But if the circumstances require it, we have to see that the widow is provided for one year.
I don't want to be able to do that.
Go back to the tattoo.
Go ahead.
I was wondering in sort of work, there's a role that talks about the documenting special
will that we can't think of any kind of writing.
I was wondering if that's kind of what it's referring to that.
Sir, for me?
Yes, sir.
Talk about dividing the state after conducting any special, after conducting any special.
I was wondering if that's what they would be referring to.
>> Well, at this affairs, talk about the secret charity.
And now that you think about the kingdom of secret windows,
you want to guarantee that I know of two instances where people,
the matter would have to specify that charity can be supported.
All of her is alive, as nobody knows about it.
She must have a year to support.
So the Quran's come was also constructed.
Yeah, it's very, yeah, so, so, so good, you see.
It's very, it's very, very general.
And if we're going to details,
you will see how good this is.
For example, I have two eyes,
because you must make allowance.
Unfortunately, they only have one, but anyhow.
(audience laughing)
Hypothetically, suppose I have,
I have, I leave two windows behind.
>> Two letters.
>> Yeah, I know.
[ Laughter ]
What can I do?
>> Just wait till the rumors start.
>> Yeah.
>> I think my book has two parts.
>> Suppose I leave two widows behind.
This might apply only to one of the widows.
For example, if widows A has no children,
But we know being has a has children.
And the children will take over the household.
So maybe we know one.
That's not one to stay in that house.
She wants to go back to her father or to her brother.
Because this case we're not happy to read the two.
We do two would like to stay in that household.
So there's not-- it's not a problem for we do two.
It might be a problem for we know one.
Maybe in Charlotte, we do three, and we do four.
[ Laughter ]
But it's very, very interesting phenomena.
It makes a lot of us for those who want to leave the house home.
But if a man has only one widow, and that widow is with the children,
the children take over the household, then this will not be a plan.
Because she loves to stay with the children.
That is a household.
>> So that takes care of more than one wife.
It's general and how to take care of the community.
(muffled speaking)
Any person that you can come with or
has to provide support for one year, if they move,
just to get a guarantee of support.
(muffled speaking)
- I think it's your answer to her.
It's like the game of chess.
It's a game of chess because I can buy
a insurance K1 installment of $200
and cast $100,000 in this month.
- Why?
- It's a game of chess.
(muffled speaking)
- That kind of who puts sign on his wife's.
- Yeah.
- He had bought, he was buying insurance for her
a month before.
- Oh, another one in, nothing too strong.
(muffled speaking)
This lady, she shut her husband
in the office parking lot.
Then she had the chip.
Could be mine.
- Yeah, then too.
- The sure of the squire.
(audience laughs)
And Jesus also.
- Very one plan.
(audience laughs)
- No, I don't know if you have to go,
but in Islamic law, at least in the Philippines,
this woman cannot inherit one single cent
from the man she killed.
She can attack.
His brother, his children can inherit it, but the person who kills such a man,
she cannot accept it. No judge in the Philippines.
It's a little bit worse than divorce.
It's not a divorce, you know.
It's a little bit worse.
She's not just life anymore.
This is probably too far, but more about the hatred and not the violence.
It's not a matter of the whole government.
Yeah, on demand attorney insurance folks,
we have a question about it.
Here's what I'm going to do, but I don't know.
I'm not going to hold me legally responsible for it.
They started, as Andrew first, by demanding
that you have a lot of eyes that are
active evidence that you sign a paper saying
that you are insured.
But they found that there's too much work.
And now the law is that all you need to sign a paper saying
I am insured.
Now I will go and I will sign a paper to send insul with Allah.
And if they want the last four numbers, I have to do it.
Now if they catch me later on and they say, "Hey, you're going to have insurance."
This is surgery or something.
I'll prove to them, because I have insurance with Allah.
And this is what I call, "Now we have to put the cup handy."
If they have the time to listen, I will show them.
Because we do have insurance on that.
And it is the best insurance in that.
You do not have accidents.
How do they do that?
I have to say, how do they do that?
Because I don't want to go out there and have an accident.
[LAUGHTER]
OK.
The difference between guards insurance and insurance companies
insurance.
With the government insurance insurance companies,
you would have accidents and they would pay for you.
If you have insurance for the law, you're looking at the assets historically.
So, remember, insurance handled in fact,
there were more people from bearing the values than others.
Back to the two.
I think we should be performing one more.
So, the element is actually here in order to make the element is
Everybody is fiftieth to fight, and it's not a crime.
But about the amount.
The amount is really dependent on how much you can afford.
And what's the husband's enough for?
It's just up to you.
But for the divorce, there's equitable elimination people
provided.
This is an incumbent beautiful upon the race.
So I think I also hope it can be how long the marriage lasts.
It's what you feel.
What you feel is that it's an incumbent duty upon the righteous.
The righteous people will be responsible for it, and you have to go a little bit more against yourself.
When the person has paid the money,
so you think they can afford $50 and go on $75.
It's fine to get good.
It's got to recommendation.
What is the process mean?
Is it also for the man who is treated for the woman?
Does anybody in the film think of a woman?
You know, it opens a kind of world.
[LAUGHTER]
(laughter)
No, this is for the women.
It's because the Arabic, the Arabic shows the feminine,
the most women, the most serious.
Does the man talk about the Bible also?
- Yeah. - Uh-oh.
May I, uh...
In my next translation, I've said the most women who are in the Arabic is very specific.
May I mention something about also the Islamic spirit?
Actually, in many cases, Islam discriminates against the men.
It's in favor of the woman.
I'll explain why.
It's a bit right for us.
That's why I say, she has to refer only to women, can't be a man.
Because the one who pronounces the divorce is the man.
And therefore in any case, the woman is the agreed party.
And that's when actual practice, when a woman is, let's say, maltreated by a husband, etc., etc., etc.,
she asks for a divorce from her husband. You get it?
But that's a simple question.
No, yeah.
I'm telling you how this unexpired has developed.
So, and he is...
...and if he refuses, sometimes the judge declares the divorce.
So, when she asks for a divorce, and he refuses the judge's declaration for him,
or he grants the... I mean, he makes the divorce.
So in any case, even if the woman is the one who wants the divorce or wants to be divorced,
since it's the husband who declares the divorce, she is the agreed party.
And therefore, strictly speaking, islam.
Only a woman is a divorcee.
This has to be a woman.
A woman cannot tell a man, "I divorce you," husband knows.
She can make his life so miserable that he divorces her.
Then she gets what she wants.
Because she can all say, "Well, you divorce me.
You must give me my dowry.
If you have kept it, you must give me this, this, this."
So it's always, I think, Islamic spirit has already seen not all the women.
I'm not complaining, you know.
But I told you that this, what you have said, that Islam has always been against women.
always been against women, I don't know, this has been a black propaganda against Islam.
And that we mentioned the idea of inheritance was only found in England, women began to
inherit in England only in the last century. And this is a whole book. In
Americans for women is found as early as 1,400 years ago.
It took the West 100 years.
Not only that.
Even the other men were discriminated,
because only the oldest one gets it.
- That's right.
- So they discriminated against women in the younger violence.
(coughing)
- I think we're the thing against them,
it's not that.
Whereas one of the bad guys
And they don't even know the difference between the people, both of them.
The President.
The conditions of consent.
The safety.
The Center realizes that the woman is half of society in a more than half.
And women raised their children.
Women are more than half of society.
And the Senate made them a target.
because of all of them to go to the private prayer.
So there are cadets against the women
going to the private prayer.
Does want them to go to the hospital?
Does want them to pray what they have meant to worship?
Does want them to pass from their restoration?
[INAUDIBLE]
So in certain concentrated of the women,
the Quran is merely going to peace the women's life.
You may find it interesting to -- that my understanding of the God is that the woman can also divorce the man.
Because of my understanding.
My understanding is the marriages and the agreement between two people.
The two people are married for as long as both of them agree that they are married.
Please, the one part of the man or the woman decides that the woman is over.
It's makes it illegal.
One party is satisfied.
But the positions back home have been a long time,
according to the map that say I did vote.
And she's the vote.
[ Inaudible ]
This is the monetary transactions in the law.
It's the law instance where you cannot have a man and the woman witnesses,
because the man can marry the woman.
[SOUND]
And you are women.
If the man marries the woman, they become like one witness.
He may influence her or she may influence him.
And they are not any more qualified as two different witnesses.
So why not?
And why would I have three witnesses?
I suppose they, you know, they're talking to me.
They're all going to say, well, you're married to two of them.
They are married to two of them.
Actually, if you married the two of them, it's still safe because
You have no idea how much the rivalry is.
It explains the two wives of what men.
When we hear all kinds of stories,
if you read a cinema book about the Rhyme Society,
the rumors about wives getting the children of the other wives
of children, the rivalry is unbelievable.
So, when the ones of the women lies about the law of action not alone,
the social justice, they're the kind of resources this is the best.
One of them did get out of the right thing.
So even in that instance, the man marries the two of the district government fees the safety of the system office.
What about, I mean if there was old male witness, if there was only women witness,
the whole transaction was just about women.
But you still need to support, huh?
That's a very serious situation.
What?
And it's very strong.
I'm thinking of the first thing.
I mean, there's a lot of women now that have business.
You let back this one of the biggest things they were talking about in the radio TV, one of the fastest growth number women with with another business.
I guess all the time.
But the first thing you have two men with, which is, are one men and two people.
So a citizen fight, a man.
Okay, back to the two.
[ Inaudible ]
>> You shall courageously struggle for the course of dance.
What do you think of those who play their homes,
though they numbered in the thousands,
because they feel death, consequently, God's safety
can die, then revise them.
That is gracious toward the people,
but not people are not appreciative.
You shall couragefully fight for the cause of God,
and know that God is still, fully aware.
which will not loan that the right is loan that he multiplies for you many four.
Well,
243.
Well, in general, we know what this means.
I don't know if it's the first particular event.
But the idea is that we have to die sooner or later.
This refers to, as I said, nobody's historical or in general,
that these are people who flee from their homes,
they are by the thousands.
And they feel that.
But anyhow, they feel that they leave their house,
but in any case, Allah made them die.
so they cannot forestall, forestall death.
Now regarding the reviving them,
this could mean in any case also,
men will be recreated.
But that will be for,
that will be on the day of judgment.
But in the very arc of creating men,
giving him a second creation, giving them man-kani,
a second creation, it's still a form of graciousness
towards them.
And people do not understand why Allah has to do just man-kind.
Why Allah has to revive us after death in Jazza.
But the commandment is clear.
Five.
Because if you are afraid, and you run away, first 243 says, in any case you will die.
You will die and Allah can make you die.
So if you are going to die, it might as well die.
This is for Māti.
Māti is going to die in a good core.
And what force is better than that of Allah?
No, this is... I've seen this.
I've seen people fight for Islam and...
Really, I've seen them die in Akhāl's...
Akhāl's dragon.
which do not know that a righteous loan, that he multiplies for you many forms.
Again, this is general, but let me make it specific.
If you are willing to give your life or the cost of a life, this is like a loan.
He will give you a better life in the year after.
And certainly, this substitution of a good life is, in paradise.
It's much better. It's a multiplication of the highest order.
Then we kind of like that short, sad, and sometimes very difficult for all of us.
So, if Allah, Imam, should life give it to him as alone.
And you will get back the interest many fall.
I know that there are times really, the United States thinks are calmer here,
but I don't know what can happen in the future.
Only and no are in the future, but in many countries there are cases when a man is asked to stand up to be counted
It's hard to talk like this, but I've seen people who have died for the course of Islam.
And they live in the memories of many of us.
And we wish hope, and actually, if enough, we believe that people like us have really marked this and they are very self-borrowed.
I think you said by the way.
Doesn't say something to someone
and if you guys are happy
or you don't know what you thought about it.
That's what I'm suggesting.
Yes.
That's right.
Thank you.
You see, when you come to New York,
you're going to have people to become war
in New York.
Yeah.
And it's mainly because
certain all those movements,
against you.
The moment you are especially if you are going to be a significant force for worshipping rather
low, you can all kinds of forces that fight you.
If you are not ready enough to stand up for those fights and be ready to press, then
you are not qualified for the result.
It is tremendous to walk the boat with you.
When the first verse, my understanding of it is verse 2, 4, 1, 2, 3, 3.
What they think of those who fled their homes, though they were numbered in 2000.
This is an actual incident in the past, my understanding of them for us.
People who believed in God and there were other people who didn't like it.
Just the way it is happening today.
So they went to attack those people and they didn't want to stand up for them.
They let their homes.
And by understanding the heart of this is one of the incidents,
where God actually let them die so they can see that death is nothing.
It's not the smoke that horrible.
And then God invites them and he makes them aware that they were dead.
What's the best experience of death and it will be part of it.
The lesson here was that not all the different children,
but so are there.
The death is nothing to be feared or nothing to worry about.
What is that you didn't describe?
It's not the best sense.
Oh, you mean that's the way you understand it.
What the hell is it?
says they were a pair of dead so they fled their home. You know one of God. So God made them die and then
they invited them. There are a few instances of dead and there's a direction to answer. First the man who was passing by a
community that was a post-town and he said help him, why do I have to wipe this after it's
going to wipe out. So God put him to this for a hundred years and then he invited him. That's one is under one.
I'm captain.
The other one is the people who were dead for 390 years.
And this is the family.
This is the family.
Right.
Go, give me.
Also, the man who, they, they put a used part of the character revival, you know. And he thought, "Who can they?"
That's another, in, there are a few instances in Toronto where God revives today.
So this is thousands of people that want to.
people who are watching.
This is thousands of people.
It's got to come in and divide.
It divides and then you'll wipe them.
And so the people who are going to do that,
because that's wasn't bad.
Actually, we all experienced death.
People who were born.
And you didn't miss everyone.
You didn't even miss them.
And you didn't care.
You weren't dead.
[laughter]
It's just the way it is.
with the way that's alive now at this point.
But we all experienced that before.
It wasn't bad, wasn't?
I'm right.
Really nothing to appear, especially if you know
that the type and place and the manner of death
is already written down because it's in your individual test,
exactly when, where and how you will die.
It's already decided.
There is nothing anybody can do to change that.
I should come here and tell you.
Come to me today, man.
I'm not too scared of it.
So, 2 by 4 says, you shall purposely fight for the cause of God and know that God is here.
So, the believer is always victorious.
By the way, excuse me, I did not.
It is 15 minutes to mine and they have to rush a little earlier today because this is interesting.
This is a long section.
I just can take the shot with her.
But, well, many of you have met my sister.
She's arriving to my...
Her husband, he got her?
Yeah.
Her husband won a scholarship to study at the university.
This is an Egyptian government scholarship.
So she'd be here for at least four years.
She's arriving on the public airlines flight number.
You guessed it, my dear.
(Laughter)
What's I think as a good size in...
I was worried about her husband.
You were a robot in Mexico now.
It was a humbleness she made.
She came today in a background and she was elected for this one, so it was nothing to do.
I wasn't sure what her husband was.
He was the main one.
He is a company here.
Oh, he is done.
I have to ask for the airport itself.
So what I did was discuss the three verses,
two four thirds for seven points.
Have you noted the elders of this realm
After the time of Moses who said to their prophets,
"A point that came for us if you want us to fight for the cause of God."
He said, "Is it your intention that when fighting is decreed for you, you will not fight?"
They said, "Why should you not fight for the cause of God when you are forcibly evicted from our homes and deprived of our children?"
Yet when fighting was decreed for them, they turned away, except for a few.
God is fully aware of the wrongdoers.
Then the Prophet said to them, "God is appointed,
"daloo to be your king."
They said, "How come he be our king?
"How could he be our king when we are more worthy of kingship
"than he is, and he is not rich?"
He said, "God has chosen him and endowed him
"with abundance in both mind and body.
"God grants kingship to whomever he wills.
"God is vaunches and mission."
The Prophet said to them, "The sign of his kingship is that the art of the covenant will
come to you, bring assurance from your Lord and relic from the time of Moses and Aaron.
The angels will bring it to you.
They should be a convincing sign for you if you are really believers."
One of the points I think, this is just here, is that the material, well, it's not the right
here and produce for God to be a person for a certain mission.
It's also a description of people who might say things without actually meaning it.
it, you know, same things that were put into you. Like these people who said they would,
why not, why wouldn't we fight for God when, but actually, you know, they did, some of
them didn't, many of them didn't.
This of course is a historical incident nourishing of how swords become a thing, and it is identical
to what's in the Bible.
I believe the Bible got solved.
You find that it is identical to the sword, the objective of the word of sword, the king,
when he is not rich.
to then material rights is the most important thing,
and what distinguishes the person from another.
But the criterion for distinguishing the one people
as far as God is concerned is righteousness, as you know.
And also, the kind that was followed,
the Bible says he's a head-filler
than any of you in this Bible.
So the story here is identical to what we see in the Bible.
Also, in order there's an essence of the art.
Did they even see the movie?
[LAUGHTER]
So there's some throws to the movie.
The movie.
What's the name of the movie after the great?
Brothers of the Lost Art.
The art has tremendous power associated with it.
It has a bit different faces to it.
What is very interesting is that the Quran reveals that many people have asked,
"What is inside?"
The Quran says that these are ready after the Lord now, remember.
These are things belonging to Moses and Eilom, which in time goes as far as...
What do you have to tell them about?
What do you have to tell them about God?
[ Inaudible ], but I'm not sure if you've got the --, but I'm not sure if you've got the specific [inaudible]
[ Inaudible ], okay.
6 o'clock in June as well.
We're enjoying the long night.
We have a proper shopping board once.
This is an awesome thing for you to chat with.
Thank you.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[INAUDIBLE]
[END PLAYBACK]
(buzzing)